# **LOUISE FRANCOIS**

Email: lfcoding35@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/louise-francois/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/louise-francois/</a>

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/lfcoding1">https://github.com/lfcoding1</a>

I am a current student in full stack web development. I have become passionate about learning new computer languages and putting them into practice. My previous experience in sales, marketing and customer service have contributed to my being a well rounded professional suited to a junior full stack web development position.

#### **QUALIFICATIONS**

- Hack Your Future, Malmo Sweden: Current student of full stack web development.
- Sacred Heart College, Kyneton Australia: Completion of high school certificate (similar to A levels).
- Alliance Française, Paris France: French levels A1, A2.
- Cours Municipaux d'Adultes, Paris France: French level B1.
- **SFI Komvux, Lund Sweden**: Current student of beginner Swedish.
- **Australian College of Natural Medicine Melbourne Australia:** Certificate IV in Remedial Therapy.
- **MEGT:** Certificate III in Retail Supervision.
- **TAFE Queensland:** Certificate III in Public Safety (Community Safety).

### **COMPUTER SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- React and other JavaScript frameworks
- Databases (MySQL)
- Github
- CLI

#### **LANGUAGES**

• **English**: English mother tongue

• **French:** Intermediate level

• **Swedish:** beginner student of Swedish

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2015-2019 Hard working mother to two wonderful children

#### 2013-2015 -Sight Seeker's Delight, Paris France

Walking Tour Guide

- English speaking walking tour guide
- Animated and entertaining debates on the history and culture of France
- Walking tours to major sites in Paris city centre

## 2011-2012 - Intrepid Travel, Melbourne Australia

Insides sales reservations agent

- Reservations for tours offered throughout the world, particularly in Europe, South America, Australia, Asia
- Assistance for other tourism professionals in creating and maintaining reservations for their clients
- Knowledge of travel based computer software and booking systems
- Direction and aide for clients whilst on tour.

### 2010-2011 - Australian Wine Tour Company, Yarra Valley, Australia

Strategist for sales and marketing

- Creating new concepts and ideas to apply to the advertising/ marketing campaigns
- Implementation of marketing strategies
- Sourcing new clientele and increasing productivity of the company on a domestic and international level
- Tour guide in the Victorian wine region of Australia

### 2008-2010 - Australian Pacific Touring, Melbourne Australia

Business Development Executive and National Day Tours Consultant

- Developing marketing campaigns
- Maintaining current sales relationships with a variety of hotels and booking agents in Victoria, Australia
- Logistics for domestic tour groups and ensuring the smooth flow of their day tours

### 2007 - Tour Guide pour Contiki Holidays ltd, UK and Europe

Tour Guide in Europe for groups of 18-35 year old adults.

- Leading groups of English speaking tourists on tours between 10 -40 days in length throughout Europe (focus on central and western Europe)
- · Organising activities and conducting walking and driving tours of major capital cities
- Keeper of accounts and tour funds for each tour